<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Ocyan - Cloud-Native Blockchain Infrastructure &amp; Analytics</title>
    <link>/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Ocyan - Cloud-Native Blockchain Infrastructure &amp; Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (C) Evalonlabs LTD - All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scale Up</title>
      <link>/product/scale-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product/scale-up/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insights</title>
      <link>/product/insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product/insights/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Plan</title>
      <link>/product/partnership-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 17:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product/partnership-plan/</guid>
      <description>Solution Partnerships Discover scalable and secure solutions that will empower you to achieve your business and client needs with Ocyan Partner Network. Customer ready solutions can be deployed quickly and be extended to your bespoke needs, to accelerate your DLT transformation.

Open Platform learn more  Scale as you go No set-up - SaaS Bandwidth cost HTTP API Integration  Join Waiting List  
Enterprise-Ready learn more  On-prem Automation On-prem Cloud Service No Bandwidth cost Direct Cloud-Native Integration  Contact us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/product/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 16:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Test this is the getting started page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ocyan Features</title>
      <link>/product/ocyan-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product/ocyan-features/</guid>
      <description>Ocyan as Cloud-Native solution Ocyan is a cloud-managed solution that provides all the required infrastructure, automation, monitoring, integrations and analytics, beyond just a Blockchain as a Service, to give organizations the ability to bridge the visibility, ease to integrate and scale across their cloud architectures to any DLT/Blockchain network. Because modern applications are distributed with business operations and data spread across multiple managed services and APIs, automating the required DLT nodes is not enough.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>